Guide to the Eastern Parkway Coalition records 2007.016
Brooklyn Historical Society
Eastern Parkway Coalition records
1952-2007
1970-2007
Brooklyn Historical Society
Lesold, Constance
2007.016
10.44 Linear Feet in eight record cartons, one oversize flat box, ten flat file folders, and two rolled storage boxes.
The collection is composed of the records of the Eastern Parkway Coalition, dating from 1952 to 2007 (bulk dates, 1970-2007). These records are primarily composed of Constance Lesold's subject files. The subject files document many issues which affected the Crown Heights and Prospect Heights neighborhoods of Brooklyn. These issues include community gardens, housing/tenant rights, mass transit, summer youth programs, environmentalism, mental health, public parks, and urban renewal. In addition to subject files, the records include a series of plans and maps for the reconstruction of Eastern Parkway and other streets in the area from the 1970s and 1980s.
Scope and Contents note
The collection is composed of Constance Lesold's records of the Eastern Parkway Coalition, dating from 1952 to 2007 (bulk dates, 1970-2007). These records are primarily composed of subject files, which document issues that affected the Crown Heights and Prospect Heights neighborhoods of Brooklyn. These issues include include community gardens, housing/tenant rights, mass transit, summer youth programs, drug use, environmentalism, mental health, public parks, and urban renewal. In addition to subject files, the records include a series of plans and maps for the reconstruction of Eastern Parkway and other streets in the area.
Conditions Governing Access note
Open to users without restriction.
Arrangement
The records are organized into two series:
Series 1: Subject files, 1952-2007
Series 2: Plans and maps, 1973-1988
Historical note
The Eastern Parkway Coalition (EPC) is a community organization based in the Crown Heights neighborhood of Brooklyn. Established in the 1970s, the organization ran summer youth programs, many of which focused on community improvement and gardening. The group established a community garden atop the Franklin Avenue Shuttle subway station at the Botanic Garden/Eastern Parkway/Union Street. In 1989, New York City Transit Police demolished the community garden with the intention of clearing the land for a parking lot. The garden was later reestablished due to community outrage and is now known as the Union Street Garden and Community Development.
Biographical note
Constance "Connie" Lesold was born in North Carolina in 1938. She first visited the Brooklyn neighborhood of Crown Heights in 1966 and had an apartment with her husband, Helmuth Lesold, by 1967. The couple had one son, Benjamin, who was born in 1970. She is a social worker, who was president of the Parkway Independent Democrats and an official of Community Board Eight. Along with her husband, several Brooklyn community boards, the Brooklyn Botanic Garden, and a public coalition, she opposed the Metropolitan Transportation Authority's move to end service on the Franklin Avenue Shuttle in the mid-1990s. She volunteered with the Brooklyn Mental Hygiene Court Monitors Project and became a member of Disabled in Action. In 2004, she joined a group occupying a firehouse that shut down service in Williamsburg. Lesold joined lawmakers and citizens at the Capitol in Albany to protest rent control regulations in 2015 and she remains an active participant in MTA Board hearings.
Related Materials
Center for Brooklyn History holds the following related materials:
- Antonia Denis collection, 1948–1983 (1992.021)
- Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation Oral History collection, 2007-2008 (2008.030)
- West Indian Carnival Documentation Project records, 1993-1996 (2010.019)
- Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation publication and photograph collection, 1968–2007 (ARC.124)
- Brooklyn neighborhood associations and civic organizations publications, 1881-2010 (ARC.167)
- Junior League of Brooklyn records, 1910-2002 (ARC.304)
- Voices of Crown Heights oral histories, 2016-2017 (2016.027)
- Listen to This: Crown Heights Oral History collection, 2010 (2010.020)
The New York Public Library holds the following related materials:
- NYPIRG Straphangers Campaign records, 1962-2007 (MssCol 6147)
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Constance Lesold, 2007.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Most of the materials in Series 2: Plans and maps are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use. Please contact cbhreference@bklynlibrary.org for more information about access.
Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.); Audiocassettes; Community activists -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Clippings (information artifacts); Haitian Americans -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Housing -- New York (State) -- Kings County; African Americans -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Gateway National Recreation Area (N.J. and N.Y.); Mental health services -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Newsletters; Local transit -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Maps; Posters; Prospect Heights (New York, N.Y.); Parks -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Photographs; Tenants' associations -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Urban beautification -- New York (State) -- Kings County; West Indian Americans -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Social justice -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Streets -- New York (State) -- Kings County -- Design and construction; Subway stations -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Subways -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Dutch elm disease -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Eastern Parkway (New York, N.Y.); Environmentalism -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Community development -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Community gardens -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Correspondence; Crown Heights (New York, N.Y.); Reports; Prospect Park (New York, N.Y.); Eastern Parkway Coalition Garden (New York, N.Y.); Blueprints (reprographic copies); Eastern Parkway Coalition; Community Board No. 9 (Brooklyn, New York, N.Y.); Community Board No. 8 (Brooklyn, New York, N.Y.); Brooklyn Tenants Union Incorporated (New York, N.Y.); Brooklyn Museum; Brooklyn Botanic Garden; Kingsboro Psychiatric Center; City University of New York. Medgar Evers College; West Indian American Day Carnival Parade (Brooklyn, N.Y.); Greens/Green Party USA; Parks Council (New York, N.Y.); New York (N.Y.). Department of Parks and Recreation; New York (State). Metropolitan Transportation Authority; Lesold, Constance; Lesold, Helmuth; Lesold, Constance
- Series 1: Subject files, 1952-2007; 1970-2007
  Scope and Contents
  The series contains subject files of Constance Lesold's work with the Eastern Parkway Coalition and includes documents dating from 1952 to 2007.
  The files were maintained by Constance Lesold, who was also an active member of other community groups, such as Community Boards 8 and 9, the Brooklyn Tenants Union, and local block associations. Files related to those other organizations appear frequently in the series.
  The series documents several topics relating to the Crown Heights and Prospect Heights neighborhoods of Brooklyn from the 1970s to the early 2000s. These subjects include community gardens, housing/tenant rights, mass transit, summer youth programs, drug use, environmentalism, mental health, public parks, the Haitian community, and urban renewal.
  Community gardens are especially well represented in the files, especially the Franklin Avenue Shuttle Garden, which was demolished by the Metropolitan Transportation Authority (MTA) in 1989. Controversy over the Brooklyn Botanic Garden charging entrance fees is also addressed in the series.
  Cultural affairs are also featured in the series, especially the Brooklyn Museum, the Brooklyn Public Library, and the New Muse.
  The files are primarily composed of flyers, publications, correspondence, memoranda, and clippings. A small amount of files include photographs, slides, negatives, and audio cassettes.
  Arrangement
  The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
  - [Clippings, correspondence, and banner], 1981-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - [MTA correspondence], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Parkway news articles and publications, 1973-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Urban Park Rangers, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Tree Tips, 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - [Hand drawn Eastern Parkway Coalition Garden map], circa 1980s (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Air and noise pollution, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Growing herbs and vegetables, 1975-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Container gardening, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Wild plants, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - House plants and poisonous plants, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Endangered species, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Birds, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Butterfly, circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Zoos, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Dogs, circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Mouse care information, circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Planetaria, 1952-1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Timed materials, City lot (Council on Environment), circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Flowers, circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Insects and diseases, circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - [Gardening] tools, circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Watering tips, circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Soil and compost, circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Ground covers and vines, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Berries, circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Eastern Parkway complaint form, circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Other groups' on the parkway events, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Municipal Arts Society, 1982, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Squibb and Van Vorhees Parks, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Community gardens, 1977-1981 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Local group purchasing energy, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Horticultural society, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - NY Street Tree Consortium, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Gateway [National Recreation Area], 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Al-Karim School, circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - 274 St. Johns Place and Grand Army Plaza, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Boro budget meetings, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Community Board 8, 1978-1984, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - [Flyers, publications, clippings], 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - [Clippings], 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - [Flyers, publications, clippings], 1977-2006 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - [Brooklyn Botanic Garden even photographs], circa 2000 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - [Lincoln Place and Eastern Parkway united neighborhood block association], 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    This folder includes Crown Heights housing and landlord-tenant complaints.
  - Obituaries, 1983-1991 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - [Mount Prospect Park], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Brooklyn Botanic Garden fees / protests, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Brooklyn Botanic Garden and Prospect Park, 1980-2002 (Box 1, Folder 48 - 49)
  - Park Slope and Brooklyn Greens, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - [New York City Committee on Health / American Lung Association], 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    This folder includes materials from the Pediatric Asthma Center.
  - [New York City Department of Environmental Protection meetings], 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Herbicides and Pesticides, 1999-2006 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Pesticides and West Nile Virus, 1998-2006 (Box 2, Folder 4 - 5, Box OS-42, Folder 12)
    This folder includes newsletters and flyers from the Green Party.
  - [Pesticides], 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 6 - 7)
  - Black Music Association, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - New Muse, 1973-1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - [Lincoln Place United Block Association and New Muse], 1974-1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    General
    This folder includes material related to Arthur Miller and Nostrand Avenue Community Commerce Association.
  - [Lincoln Place United Block Association and New Muse], 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    This folder includes photographs.
  - Maps, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 12, Box OS-42, Folder 11)
    This folder includes district maps, Jimmy Carter election flyers, Woodrow Lewis election flyers, flyers and materials related to local politics, and flyers and materials related to a budget cut at Medgar Evers College.
  - Community Board 8 - Structure and membership, 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - CD V hearings material, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 14, Box OS-42, Folder 10)
    This folder includes materials related to community development grants, Community Board 8, New Muse, Arthur Miller, and Nostrand Avenue Community Commerce. Association
  - Community Board 8 press release, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Programs and proposals by various organizations, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    This folder includes materials about drug abuse prevention.
  - Drug abuse prevention, 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    This folder includes materials published by the 77th Precinct Community Council and the Crown Heights Youth Center.
  - [Eastern Parkway Coalition, Brooklyn Tenants Union, The Muse, and other organizations], 1977-1979, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    This folder includes materials related to St. John's Recreation Center and Haitian American Day Care Center.
  - Phoenix Center correspondence, 1970-1973, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - [League of Women Voters of the City of New York election booklets], 1978-1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - [Brooklyn Botanic Garden - Dutch Elm Disease], 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - [Fix Eastern Parkway petition form], 1992 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Library kiosks - Brooklyn Tenants Union, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    This folder includes materials related to the Self-Help Neighborhood Awards Program (SNAP) Award.
  - Brooklyn Tenants Union - Meetings attended by board and staff members, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    This folder includes materials related to various Crown Heights community groups, including The East.
  - Brooklyn Tenants Union - Publicity, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    This folder includes reports on rent strikes.
  - [Children's issues], 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - [Newsletters, publications, clippings], 1973-1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    This folder includes materials related to community groups and gardening.
  - [Flyers, publications, clippings], 1999-2007 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    This folder includes materials related to Brooklyn Botanic Garden fees.
  - Summer Youth Program, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 3 - 4)
  - Summer Youth Program - Garden time sheets, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - [Flyers, newsletters, clippings], 1981-1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Franklin Avenue Shuttle and garden; includes photographs
  - Eastern Parkway, 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    This folder includes correspondence and memos from Community Board 8.
  - Eastern Parkway Area Committee, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Street tree pruning and maintenance course, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Eastern Parkway Coalition - Notice of meetings and events on Parkway, 1978-1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Eastern Parkway Coalition - Garden correspondence, 1978-1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    This folder includes a 1979 lease for the lot for the Franklin Avenue Shuttle Garden.
  - Eastern Parkway Coalition - Planning ideas, 1977-1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Bills and receipts, 1979-1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Community Board 8 - Parks Committee, 1979-1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Eastern Parkway Coalition stationery, circa 1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - [GreenThumb newsletters], 1978-1989 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Eastern Parkway Coalition applications, circa 1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    This folder includes a membership and field trip form.
  - [Community Board 8 - Environmental fairs, apartheid protest, and other events], 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Merchant appeals, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Dutch Elm trees pamphlets and survey, 1973-1982 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Operation Greenthumb, 1979-1986 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Eastern Parkway Coalition - Correspondence and newsletters, 1979-1984 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    This folder includes materials related to Dutch Elms and the Franklin Avenue Shuttle.
  - Eastern Parkway Coalition - Meetings attended, 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Franklin Avenue Shuttle Community Garden, 1979-1984 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Franklin Avenue Shuttle Community Garden - Summer programs, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - West Indian Day Carnival, 1979-1983 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Black Spectrum Theater and other Coalition groups, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - [Crown Heights Board of Community Affairs], 1971-1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Grant Square, 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Grants information, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Trust for Public Land and Neighborhood Open Space Coalition, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Brooklyn Museum, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Parks Council, 1978-1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    This folder includes a photograph with Constance Lesold.
  - Magnolia Tree Earth Center, 1975-1985 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Council on the Environment, 1974-1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    This folder includes materials related to the Greenmarket farmers market program.
  - Environmental Defense Fund and Environmental Action Coalition, 1974, circa 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Weeksville, 1975-1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Extension [Cornell Cooperative Extension], 1977-1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Green Guerilla, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Drug Abuse Prevention Proposal Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Children's projects, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Other landmark groups, 1978-1984 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - [Crown Heights - Area Maintenance Program], 1972-1976 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Crown Heights newsletters, 1971-1977 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - [New York City Community Planning Districts], 1973-1977 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Registered Democrats, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - [Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA)], 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 22 - 23)
    These folders include materials related to New Muse, Brooklyn Tenants Union, and Brooklyn Renaissance Coalition for Jobs.
  - [Clippings and flyers], 1969-1983 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Beware of Elms in Thunder audio recordings, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Two audio cassette tapes, also includes Gail Guillet, NYC Landmarks Commission, NPR, Bilingual Education Conference, and universal identity card
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    These undigitized audio cassette tapes are not available for research.
  - Artists of the Eastern Parkway Coalition - Beware of Elms in Thunder sign, circa 1980 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Kingsboro and Mental Health, 1976-1981 (Box 4, Folder 26 - 28)
    These folders include materials regarding the Brooklyn Tenants Union and Brooklyn Association for Mental Health.
  - [Brooklyn Tenants Union - Rent strikes], 1966-1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Recent housing and CD [Community Development] materials, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Tenants Union - Summer Youth Program, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Notes of Executive Board meetings and membership, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    The materials in this folder are related to the Brooklyn Tenants Union.
  - Incorporation papers, by-laws, and finances, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Fire, 1982-1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Brooklyn Community Council and Black Community Congress of Central Brooklyn, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Brooklyn Tenants Union, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - [Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) applicants], 1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - [Albany bus trip], 1977 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Personnel information, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - BTU [Brooklyn Tenants Union] - Other current projects, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - People's Housing Network, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Census tracts, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Old membership list, circa 1976 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Current material on Coalition, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Proposals writing, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Campaign for Human Development, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Proposals, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Progress Reports [newsletter], 1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - [Calendar of the Board of Estimate of the City of New York], 1977 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - [Calendar of the Board of Estimate of the City of New York], 1977 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Brooklyn Tenants Union stamp, circa 1978 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - [New York City Housing Authority - Welcome to your Home], circa 1978 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    This folder contains a children's activity book.
  - Brooklyn Botanic Garden - Fee issues, 1993-2002 (Box 5, Folder 24 - 26)
    This folder includes photographs of events and activities at the Brooklyn Botanic Garden.
  - Lesold - Community Board 8 Parks Committee correspondence, 1973-2002 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    This folder includes photographs of people working in a garden.
  - [Magnolia Tree Earth Center], 1990-1991, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - [Flyers, newsletters, clippings], 1997-2005 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    This folder includes flyers, newsletters, and clippings related to Medgar Evers College, the Parks Department budget, community gardens, McCarren Park, and St. Johns Recreation Center.
  - [Calendar of the Board of Estimate of the City of New York and census], 1978 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Brooklyn 2000 - State of the Borough, circa 2000 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Youth Committee, 1980-1983 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - [Youth Programs], 1980-1984 (Box 5, Folder 33 - 35, Box OS-42, Folder 9)
  - Recreation Misc., circa 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - [Brooklyn Botanic Garden and Haitian advocacy groups], 1986-2006 (Box 6, Folder 2 - 4)
    These folders also include other Crown Heights organizations.
  - [The Haitian Academy, L'Académie Haïtienne], 2006 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - [Eastern Parkway Coalition exhibition at New Muse and photographs], 1975-1980 (Box 6, Folder 6 - 8)
    The photographs included in these folders may have been exhibited as a part of the exhibition. The photographs depict dying elms, unidentified garden clean-up and advocacy events, a Lincoln Terrace Park clean-up event, installation of historic markers along Eastern Parkway, and a protest against the closing of the Franklin Avenue Shuttle. Hattie Carthan and Ruth Goring are in some of these photographs.
  - [Lincoln Terrace Park event photographs], 1984 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - [Haiti], 1987-1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - [Brooklyn Botanic Garden and Haitian advocacy groups], 1986-1990 (Box 6, Folder 11, Box OS-42, Folder 8)
  - Haitian-American Citizens for Action (HACFA) financial aid, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - [Brooklyn Botanic Garden publications], 1981-1999 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - [Botanic Gardens Conservation magazine], 1996 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - [Garden publications], circa 1996 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - [Eastern Parkway Coalition flyers, memoranda, and tree records], 1979-1996 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - [Visits to Haiti], 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 17 - 18)
  - [Visit to Haiti photographs], 1996 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - [Community flyers], 1980-2006 (Box 6, Folder 20 - 21)
  - [Reference letters], 1989 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - [EPS Garden Party photographs], 2006 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - [Eastern Parkway Coalition, Brooklyn Botanic Garden, Haitian groups, and other organizations], 1980-2006 (Box 6, Folder 24, Box OS-42, Folder 7)
  - [Grand Jury Repression], 1978 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Jackson Point Du Jour, 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Haitian Coalition on AIDS cassette tape, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Original Format: compact audio cassette, Duration: 36:53
    Two preservation .WAV files. Two access .mp3 files.
    Cassette tapes are not available for research use. Access to the interview is available online on the Internet Archive.